[{"answer": "The debate is December 27th.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 4, "question": "Does anyone still want the Trump seal of approval?", "qSentId": 3}, {"answer": "Well, I don't really care, but I don't think I'm getting it too much.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "Why is that and do you care?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "Yes, he did.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "Did Mitt Romney call you himself to say he wasn't going to take part?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "Well, he couldn't have been nicer.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "And what did he -- what did he say?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "No, I won't miss that at all.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "So you're not going to miss him kissing any part of your anatomy?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Well, you have to understand, the reason I host \"Celebrity Apprentice\" and \"The Apprentice\" and it's become one of the top shows on television, and as you know, many nights, in fact, for a period of time, it was the number one show on television, and continues to get great ratings.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "What do you say to those critics in particular?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "I don't -- I think he's OK.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "Do you find him funny?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, the debate is a Newsmax debate and that's a very powerful organization, and they really are, and they've done an amazing job.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "What do you think of him?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think he said it the way you said it.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "What did you think of his point that he made?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "Well, he's really playing the class warfare very hard.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "What do you think of that as a principle?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "Well, I think there are a lot of better ways.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "Is there a better way for him to say the same thing?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "Well, I hope there's momentum.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "Is there any momentum now building even slowly in the American economy, or is this false hope, do you think?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I never flirted many times.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "I mean, are you not genuinely tempted?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Well, I don't want to say that.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "And would it be fair to say that right now it would be pretty unthinkable that you would endorse anybody outside of Romney or Gingrich?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "Would you consider being a vice president to any of these candidates?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Well, I certainly would consider that, because we need that.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "If one of these Republican candidates came to you and they became president next November, for argument's sake, and they said, look, Donald, we would like you to now be the trade negotiator for America, with China, with OPEC, and so on, would you take that job?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "Well, I think there are a lot of key issues.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "What do you think the key issues are?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "No, I don't think I -- look, first of all I know them.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "And you're going to give them a hard time, Donald, if they start taking you on and shirking the questions?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "Well, if the title -- if the word Diva means hard work, a woman that knows what she wants, and won't take no for an answer, I don't mind being that.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "Do you like that?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "I mean, I don't ask for much, you know.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "When do you really lose it?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "If my dressing room is cold.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "What are the little things that can really drive you bonkers?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "If it's freezing, you know, if it's like super cold, uncomfortable.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "How cold does it have to be before you explode?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "I have to have lemon and honey.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "What do you have to have?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Well, the licorice, it moistens your vocal chords.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "What do Twizzlers do?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "So if I eat loads of Gummy Bears, would I suddenly get a huge voice like you?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "It is very important.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Is it that kind of thing that you crave?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "LIGE: My first thought is God, thank you, because without you, there is no people.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Who are the people you think of first?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "I think about my mom, automatically.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "The individuals who have been there for you when it's really mattered?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "To be clean, to be clean, to keep our bodies clean, to wear clean underwear.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "What were the values that meant most to her, do you think, that she instilled in you?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "My mom is very proud of me.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "What does she make of what you've achieved?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Well, she's not surprised.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "Or did she always think that she had a little live wire that had an amazing talent that may one day lead to this?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "You know, I was.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "ORGAN: Are you shocked?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "I love my dad.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "Well, what feelings do you have to your father?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Well, it was exactly that, because I was making a turning point in my life.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "What was it like for you, at that moment?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "The tipping point was during the \"No More Drama\" album -- that album cycle, because I feel that I had drank myself -- like that was it.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "What was the tipping point for you?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "Yeah, so when it finally happened, I was like, wait a minute, this is not what I want.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "But you felt you were going to die?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Who abused you?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "I feel that I owe him my love.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "How much do you feel you owe Martin Kendu Isaacs, your husband now?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "I don't owe him my life.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "And your life, potentially?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "I know.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "When you look at what happened to Amy Winehouse, do you think that could have been you, if things had played out a different way for you?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "When a moment for all African-Americans, I mean, around the world, never mine just America, right?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "Did you talk to him, the president?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "I said I love you.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "What did you say?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "I think he's dealing with it pretty good, given the situation -- the situation he was put in and the mess that was thrown on him.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "How do you think he's been dealing with it?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "I believe he's capable of doing -- of having another chance.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "Do you think, if given another chance, if he's re-elected, he can do perhaps what he wanted to do from the start but has been restricted from doing?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "Larry David makes me laugh.", "docId": "111207pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "On TV or whatever, who makes you laugh?", "qSentId": 642}]